A Guide to the Goochland County (Va.) Judgments, 1728-1912
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Goochland County (Va.) Judgments, 1728-1912
The Library of Virginia
1138382-1138457, 1141396-1141469, 1144774-1144831, 1147043
94.05 cu. ft. (209 boxes)
Goochland County (Va.) Circuit Court.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in shipments of court papers from Goochland County.
Historical Information
Goochland County was formed in 1728 from Henrico County.
The Goochland County (Va.) Judgments described in this collection were created by the following courts: County Court, Superior Court of Law, Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery, and Circuit Court.
Scope and Content
Goochland County (Va.) Judgments, 1728-1912, contain civil cases in which justice was administered on the strictly formulated rules of common law. The majority of cases in this record series relate to matters of debt.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Goochland County (Va.) Circuit Court.
Subjects:
Civil procedure--Virginia--Goochland County.; Debt--Virginia--Goochland County.; Decisions--Virginia--Goochland County.; Public Records--Virginia--Goochland County.
Geographical Names:
Goochland County (Va.)--History.
Genre and Form Terms:
Judicial records--Virginia--Goochland County.; Local government records--Virginia--Goochland County.
Added Entry - Corporate Names:
Goochland County (Va.) Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery.; Goochland County (Va.) County Court.; Goochland County (Va.) Superior Court of Law.
Contents List
- Judgments 1728 July-Dec - 1729 Jan-March (Barcode 1138382)
- Judgments 1729 May-December (Barcode 1138383)
- Judgments 1730 (Barcode 1138384)
- Judgments 1730-1739 (Barcode 1138393)
- Judgments 1731 (Barcode 1138385)
- Judgments 1732 (Barcode 1138386)
- Judgments 1733 January-June (Barcode 1138387)
- Judgments 1733 July-December (Barcode 1147043)
- Judgments 1734 (Barcode 1138388)
- Judgments 1735 (Barcode 1138389)
- Judgments 1736 (Barcode 1138390)
- Judgments 1737 (Barcode 1138391)
- Judgments 1738 (Barcode 1138392)
- Judgments 1740 (Barcode 1138394)
- Judgments 1741 (Barcode 1138395)
- Judgments 1742 (Barcode 1138396)
- Judgments 1743 (Barcode 1138397)
- Judgments 1744 January-September (Barcode 1138398)
- Judgments 1744 Oct-Dec - 1745 Jan-June (Barcode 1138399)
- Judgments 1745 July-Dec - 1746 Jan-June (Barcode 1138400)
- Judgments 1746 July-Dec - 1747 Jan-April (Barcode 1138401)
- Judgments 1747 May-Dec (Barcode 1138402)
- Judgments 1748 (Barcode 1138403)
- Judgments 1749, fragments 1740-1749 (Barcode 1138404)
- Judgments 1750-1751 (Barcode 1138405)
- Judgments 1752 (Barcode 1138406)
- Judgments 1753-1754 (Barcode 1138407)
- Judgments 1755 (Barcode 1138408)
- Judgments 1755-1757 (Barcode 1138409)
- Judgments 1758-1759 (Barcode 1138410)
- Judgments 1760-1761 (Barcode 1138411)
- Judgments 1762 (Barcode 1138412)
- Judgments 1763 (Barcode 1138413)
- Judgments 1764 (Barcode 1138414)
- Judgments 1765 January-August (Barcode 1138415)
- Judgments 1765 September-December (Barcode 1138416)
- Judgments 1766-1767 January-June (Barcode 1138417)
- Judgments 1767 July-Dec - 1768 Jan-June (Barcode 1138418)
- Judgments 1768-1769 July-December (Barcode 1138419)
- Judgments 1770 July-Dec - 1771 Jan-July (Barcode 1138420)
- Judgments 1771-1772 Aug-Dec (Barcode 1138421)
- Judgments 1773 (Barcode 1138422)
- Judgments 1774-1777 (Barcode 1138423)
- Judgments 1778 (Barcode 1138424)
- Judgments 1779 - Jan-Aug 1783 (Barcode 1138425)
- Judgments 1783 - 1784 Sept-Dec (Barcode 1138426)
- Judgments 1785 (Barcode 1138427)
- Judgments 1786 January-July (Barcode 1138428)
- Judgments 1786 August (Barcode 1138429)
- Judgments 1786 Sept-Dec - 1787 Jan-Feb (Barcode 1138430)
- Judgments 1787 March (Barcode 1138431)
- Judgments 1787 April-July (Barcode 1138432)
- Judgments 1787 August-Dec (Barcode 1138433)
- Judgments 1788 Jan-April (Barcode 1138434)
- Judgments 1788 May-Dec (Barcode 1138435)
- Judgments 1789 January-October (Barcode 1138436)
- Judgments 1789 Nov-Dec - 1790 Jan-March (Barcode 1138437)
- Judgments 1790 April-Dec (Barcode 1138438)
- Judgments 1791 Jan-July (Barcode 1138439)
- Judgments 1791 August-Dec (Barcode 1138440)
- Judgments 1792 Jan-July (Barcode 1138441)
- Judgments 1792 August-December (Barcode 1138442)
- Judgments 1793 January-July (Barcode 1138443)
- Judgments 1793 August-December (Barcode 1138444)
- Judgments 1794 January-May (Barcode 1138445)
- Judgments 1794 June-October (Barcode 1138446)
- Judgments 1794 Nov-Dec - 1795 Jan-March (Barcode 1138447)
- Judgments 1795 April-Oct (Barcode 1138448)
- Judgments 1795 Nov-Dec - 1796 Jan-March (Barcode 1138449)
- Judgments 1796 April-October (Barcode 1138450)
- Judgments 1796 Nov-Dec - 1797 Jan-April (Barcode 1138451)
- Judgments 1797 May-October (Barcode 1138452)
- Judgments 1797 Nov-Dec - 1798 Jan-April (Barcode 1138453)
- Judgments 1798 May-October (Barcode 1138454)
- Judgments 1798 Nov-Dec - 1799 Jan-March (Barcode 1138455)
- Judgments 1799 April-August (Barcode 1138456)
- Judgments 1799 Sept-December (Barcode 1138457)
- Judgments 1800 January-May (Barcode 1141396)
- Judgments 1800 June-December (Barcode 1141397)
- Judgments 1801 January-April (Barcode 1141398)
- Judgments 1801 May-October (Barcode 1141399)
- Judgments 1801-1802 November-March (Barcode 1141400)
- Judgments 1802 April-August (Barcode 1141401)
- Judgments 1802 September-December (Barcode 1141402)
- Judgments 1803 January-May (Barcode 1141403)
- Judgments 1803 June-December (Barcode 1141404)
- Judgments 1804 January-July (Barcode 1141405)
- Judgments 1804 August-December (Barcode 1141406)
- Judgments 1805 January-May (Barcode 1141407)
- Judgments 1805 June-December (Barcode 1141408)
- Judgments 1806 January-May (Barcode 1141409)
- Judgments 1806 June-October (Barcode 1141410)
- Judgments 1806-1807 November-March (Barcode 1141411)
- Judgments 1807 April-July (Barcode 1141412)
- Judgments 1807 August-November (Barcode 1141413)
- Judgments 1807-1808 December-April (Barcode 1141414)
- Judgments 1808 May-August (Barcode 1141415)
- Judgments 1808-1809 September-March (Barcode 1141416)
- Judgments 1809 April-July (Barcode 1141417)
- Judgments 1809 August-December (Barcode 1141418)
- Judgments 1810 January-May (Barcode 1141419)
- Judgments 1810 June-December (Barcode 1141420)
- Judgments 1811 January-August (Barcode 1141421)
- Judgments 1811-1812 September-March (Barcode 1141422)
- Judgments 1812 April-October (Barcode 1141423)
- Judgments 1812-1813 November-March (Barcode 1141424)
- Judgments 1813 April-December (Barcode 1141425)
- Judgments 1814 January-August (Barcode 1141426)
- Judgments 1814-1815 September-July (Barcode 1141427)
- Judgments 1815-1816 August-July (Barcode 1141428)
- Judgments 1816 August-December (Barcode 1141429)
- Judgments 1817 January-August (Barcode 1141430)
- Judgments 1817 September-December (Barcode 1141431)
- Judgments 1818 January-April (Barcode 1141432)
- Judgments 1818 May-December (Barcode 1141433)
- Judgments 1819 January-July (Barcode 1141434)
- Judgments 1819 August-December (Barcode 1141435)
- Judgments 1820 January-April (Barcode 1141436)
- Judgments 1820 May-September (Barcode 1141437)
- Judgments 1820-1821 October-March (Barcode 1141438)
- Judgments 1821 April-July (Barcode 1141439)
- Judgments 1821 August-December (Barcode 1141440)
- Judgments 1822 January-July (Barcode 1141441)
- Judgments 1822 August-December (Barcode 1141442)
- Judgments 1823 January-July (Barcode 1141443)
- Judgments 1823 August-December (Barcode 1141444)
- Judgments 1824 January-July (Barcode 1141445)
- Judgments 1824 August-December (Barcode 1141446)
- Judgments 1825 January-July (Barcode 1141447)
- Judgments 1825 August-December (Barcode 1141448)
- Judgments 1826 January-July (Barcode 1141449)
- Judgments 1826 August-December (Barcode 1141450)
- Judgments 1827 January-July (Barcode 1141451)
- Judgments 1827 August-December (Barcode 1141452)
- Judgments 1828 January-July (Barcode 1141453)
- Judgments 1828 August-December (Barcode 1141454)
- Judgments 1829 January-July (Barcode 1141455)
- Judgments 1829 August-December (Barcode 1141456)
- Judgments 1830 January-July (Barcode 1141457)
- Judgments 1830 August-December (Barcode 1141458)
- Judgments 1831 January-October (Barcode 1141459)
- Judgments 1831-1832 November-July (Barcode 1141460)
- Judgments 1832-1833 August-July (Barcode 1141461)
- Judgments 1833-1834 August-March (Barcode 1141462)
- Judgments 1834 April-December (Barcode 1141463)
- Judgments 1835 (Barcode 1141464)
- Judgments 1836 (Barcode 1141465)
- Judgments 1837 (Barcode 1141466)
- Judgments 1838 January-April (Barcode 1141467)
- Judgments 1838 May-December (Barcode 1141468)
- Judgments 1839 (Barcode 1141469)
- Judgments 1840 (Barcode 1144774)
- Judgments 1841 January - August (Barcode 1144775)
- Judgments 1841 September - December (Barcode 1144776)
- Judgments 1842 January - July (Barcode 1144777)
- Judgments 1842 August - December (Barcode 1144778)
- Judgments 1843 January - July (Barcode 1144779)
- Judgments 1843 August - December (Barcode 1144780)
- Judgments 1844 January - June (Barcode 1144781)
- Judgments 1844 July-December, 1845 Jan-March (Barcode 1144782)
- Judgments 1845 April - December (Barcode 1144783)
- Judgments 1846 (Barcode 1144784)
- Judgments 1847 (Barcode 1144785)
- Judgments 1848 (Barcode 1144786)
- Judgments 1849, see extended description (Barcode 1144787)
- Judgments 1850 (Barcode 1144788)
- Judgments 1851 (Barcode 1144789)
- Judgments 1852 (Barcode 1144790)
- Judgments 1853 (Barcode 1144791)
- Judgments 1854, 1855 January - April (Barcode 1144792)
- Judgments 1855 May-December, 1856 Jan-August (Barcode 1144793)
- Judgments 1856 Sept-December, 1857 Jan-April (Barcode 1144794)
- Judgments 1857 May-December (Barcode 1144795)
- Judgments 1858 (Barcode 1144796)
- Judgments 1859, see extended description (Barcode 1144797)
- Judgments 1860 January-December (Barcode 1144798)
- Judgments 1861 (Barcode 1144799)
- Judgments 1862-1865 (Barcode 1144800)
- Judgments 1866 (Barcode 1144801)
- Judgments 1867 January-September (Barcode 1144802)
- Judgments 1867 Oct-Dec, 1868 Jan-Sept (Barcode 1144803)
- Judgments 1868 Oct-Dec, 1869 Jan-Sept (Barcode 1144804)
- Judgments 1869 Oct-Dec, 1870 Jan-April (Barcode 1144805)
- Judgments 1870 May-Dec (Barcode 1144806)
- Judgments 1871 January-August (Barcode 1144807)
- Judgments 1871 Sept-Dec, 1872 Jan-May (Barcode 1144808)
- Judgments 1872 June-Dec, 1873 (Barcode 1144809)
- Judgments 1874 (Barcode 1144810)
- Judgments 1875 (Barcode 1144811)
- Judgments 1876 January-October (Barcode 1144812)
- Judgments 1876 Nov-Dec, 1877 Jan-Aug (Barcode 1144813)
- Judgments 1877 Sept-Dec, 1878 (Barcode 1144814)
- Judgments 1879 January-September (Barcode 1144815)
- Judgments 1879 Oct-Dec, 1880 Jan-Aug (Barcode 1144816)
- Judgments 1880 Sept-Dec, 1881 (Barcode 1144817)
- Judgments 1882-1883 (Barcode 1144818)
- Judgments 1884-1885 (Barcode 1144819)
- Judgments 1886-1887 (Barcode 1144820)
- Judgments 1888, 1889 January-April (Barcode 1144821)
- Judgments 1889 May-December, 1890 (Barcode 1144822)
- Judgments 1891-1892 (Barcode 1144823)
- Judgments 1893-1894 (Barcode 1144824)
- Judgments 1895-1896 (Barcode 1144825)
- Judgments 1897-1899 (Barcode 1144826)
- Judgments 1900-1901 (Barcode 1144827)
- Judgments 1902-1904 (Barcode 1144828)
- Judgments 1905-1907 (Barcode 1144829)
- Judgments 1908-1910 (Barcode 1144830)
- Judgments 1911-1912, see extended description (Barcode 1144831)